theinfatuation.com 2015-12-05

# Privacy Policy – The Infatuation

Last updated: June 21, 2014

## Our Policy

Welcome to the website (the “ **Site** “, which includes any mobile applications, mobile sites and tablet applications) of The Infatuation Inc., d/b/a Immaculate Infatuation and The Infatuation (together with its successors and assigns, “ **The Infatuation** “, “we”, “us” and/or “our”). This Site is operated by The Infatuation and has been created to provide information about our company, our mobile application and to provide reviews of and information about restaurants (the “ **Infatuation Services** “) to our Site visitors (“you”, “your”). This Privacy Policy sets forth The Infatuation’s policy with respect to information including personally identifiable data (“ **Personal Data** “) and other information that is collected from Site visitors and users.

## Information We Collect

When you interact with us through the Site, we may collect Personal Data and other information from you, as further described below:

### Personal Data That You Provide Through the Site:

We collect Personal Data from you when you voluntarily provide such information, such as when you contact us with inquiries, post information or comments, respond to one of our surveys, register for access to the Infatuation Services, allow us to access your location information (such as by using the GPS on your mobile device) or use certain Infatuation Services. Wherever Infatuation collects Personal Data we make an effort to provide a link to this Privacy Policy.

**By voluntarily providing us with Personal Data, you are consenting to our use of it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data to this Site, you acknowledge and agree that such Personal Data may be transferred from your current location to the offices and servers of The Infatuation and the authorized third parties referred to herein located in the United States.**

### Other Information:

### Non-Identifiable Data:

When you interact with The Infatuation through the Site, we receive and store certain personally non-identifiable information. Such information, which is collected passively using various technologies, cannot presently be used to specifically identify you. Consequently, we do not adjust or alter our Site’s automatic tracking and data collection in response to a Do Not Track signal or request. The Infatuation may store such non-identifiable information itself or such information may be included in databases owned and maintained by The Infatuation affiliates, agents or service providers. This Site may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, and the domain names of our visitors’ Internet service providers. It is important to note that no Personal Data is available or used in this process.

In operating this Site, we may use a technology called “cookies.” A cookie is a piece of information that the computer that hosts our Site gives to your browser when you access the Site. Our cookies help provide additional functionality to the Site and help us analyze Site usage more accurately. For instance, our Site may set a cookie on your browser that allows you to access the Site without needing to remember and then enter a password more than once during a visit to the Site. In all cases in which we use cookies, we will not collect Personal Data except with your permission. On most web browsers, you will find a “help” section on the toolbar. Please refer to this section for information on how to receive notification when you are receiving a new cookie and how to turn cookies off. We recommend that you leave cookies turned on because they allow you to take advantage of some of the Site’s features.

This Site may enable the use of the Adobe Flash Player. Adobe’s Flash Player is used by the vast majority of websites that offer video and other interactive content. By default, your use of the Adobe Flash Player generates “flash cookies” (also known as “persistent identification elements” or “local shared objects”). The Adobe Flash Player (and similar applications) use flash cookies to remember user settings, preferences and usage similar to the browser cookies referenced above. You can disable, delete and control the degree to which you accept flash cookies by accessing your Adobe Flash Player management tools directly through the settings manager for Adobe Flash, located [here](http://kb2.adobe.com/cps/526/52697ee8.html). If you do not allow flash cookies to take any disc space on your computer, you may not be able to take advantage of or participate in certain features on this Site.

### Aggregated Personal Data:

In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve the users of the Infatuation Services, The Infatuation may conduct research on its customer demographics, interests and behavior based on the Personal Data and other information provided to us. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis, and The Infatuation may share this aggregate data with its affiliates, agents and business partners. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. The Infatuation may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

### Location Information:

Our Service may collect and use your location information (for example, by requesting your location in your profile or by using the GPS on your mobile device) to provide certain functionality of our Service. We may use your location information in conjunction with your Personal Data or in an aggregate way, as described above in the “Aggregated Personal Data” section.

## Our Use of Your Personal Data and Other Information

The Infatuation uses the Personal Data you provide in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data for a certain reason, we may use the Personal Data in connection with the reason for which it was provided. For instance, if you contact us by e-mail, we will use the Personal Data you provide to answer your question or resolve your problem. Also, if you provide Personal Data in order to obtain access to the Infatuation Services, we will use your Personal Data to provide you with access to such services, in conjunction with such services and to monitor your use of such services. The Infatuation and its subsidiaries and affiliates (the “Infatuation Related Companies”) may also use your Personal Data and other personally non-identifiable information collected through the Site to help us improve the content and functionality of the Site, to better understand our users and to improve the Infatuation Services. The Infatuation and its affiliates may use this information to contact you in the future to tell you about services we believe will be of interest to you. If we do so, each communication we send you will contain instructions permitting you to “opt-out” of receiving future communications. In addition, if at any time you wish not to receive any future communications or you wish to have your name deleted from our mailing lists, please contact us as indicated below.

If The Infatuation intends on using any Personal Data in any manner that is not consistent with this Privacy Policy, you will be informed of such anticipated use prior to or at the time at which the Personal Data is collected.

## Our Disclosure of Your Personal Data and Other Information

The Infatuation is not in the business of selling your information. We consider this information to be a vital part of our relationship with you. There are, however, certain circumstances in which we may share your Personal Data with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below:

### Business Transfers:

As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, Personal Data may be part of the transferred assets.

### Related Companies:

We may also share your Personal Data with our Related Companies for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy.

### Agents, Consultants and Related Third Parties:

The Infatuation, like many businesses, sometimes hires other companies to perform certain business-related functions. Examples of such functions include mailing information, maintaining databases and processing payments. When we employ another company to perform a function of this nature, we only provide them with the information that they need to perform their specific function.

### Legal Requirements:

The Infatuation may disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal obligation, (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of The Infatuation, (iii) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Site or the public, or (iv) protect against legal liability.

## Your Choices

You can use the Site without providing any Personal Data. If you choose not to provide any Personal Data, you may not be able to use certain Infatuation Services.

## Exclusions

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any Personal Data collected by The Infatuation other than Personal Data collected through the Site. This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to The Infatuation through this Site or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the Site (collectively, “Public Areas”), any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, “Unsolicited Information”). All Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and The Infatuation shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, and distribute such Unsolicited Information to others without limitation or attribution.

## Children

The Infatuation does not knowingly collect Personal Data from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any Personal Data through the Site. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children never to provide Personal Data on this Site without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Data to The Infatuation through this Site, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases.

## Third Parties and Links to Other Web Sites

This Privacy Policy applies only to the Site. We do not permit third parties to collect Personal Data on our Site, but our Site may contain links to other web sites not operated or controlled by The Infatuation (the “Third Party Sites”). The policies and procedures we described here do not apply to the Third Party Sites. The links from this Site do not imply that The Infatuation endorses or has reviewed the Third Party Sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their privacy policies.

## Social Media

The Infatuation may allow you to choose to access certain social media websites and services that are owned and/or controlled by third parties (like Facebook and Twitter) (such websites and services, collectively, the “Social Media Services”) through the Site. If you elect to access and use the Social Media Services, you will be sharing your information (which will include personal information if you elect to share such information) with those Social Media Services. As with other Third Party Sites, the information that you share with the Social Media Services will be governed by the privacy policies and terms of service of the providers of such Social Media Services and not by the polices and procedures we describe here. When you add Social Media Service accounts to the Infatuation Services or log into the Site using your Social Media Services account, we will collect relevant information necessary to enable the Site to access that Social Media Service. As part of such integration, the Social Media Service will provide The Infatuation with access to certain information that you have provided to such Social Media Service, and we will use, store and disclose such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. However, please remember that the manner in which Social Media Services use, store and disclose your information is governed by the policies of the applicable Social Media Services provider, and, as a result, The Infatuation shall not have any liability or responsibility for the privacy practices or other actions of Social Media Services that may be enabled within and/or otherwise accessible through the Site.

You may also have the option of posting your Services activities to Social Media Services when you access content through the Services (for example, you may post to Facebook that you performed an activity on the Service); you acknowledge that if you choose to use this feature, your friends, followers and subscribers on any Social Media Services you have enabled will be able to view such activity.

## Security

The Infatuation takes reasonable steps to protect the Personal Data provided via the Site from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, no Internet or e-mail transmission is ever fully secure or error free. In particular, e-mail sent to or from this Site may not be secure. Therefore, you should take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail. Please keep this in mind when disclosing any Personal Data to The Infatuation via the Internet.

## Other Terms and Conditions

Your access to and use of this Site is subject to the [Terms of Service](http://www.theinfatuation.com/terms-of-service).

## Changes to The Infatuation’s Privacy Policy

The Site and our business may change from time to time. As a result, at times it may be necessary for The Infatuation to make changes to this Privacy Policy. The Infatuation reserves the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time without prior notice. Please review this policy periodically, and especially before you provide any Personal Data. This Privacy Policy was last updated on the date indicated above. Your continued use of the Site after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy.

## Access to Information; Contacting The Infatuation

You may change or update information in your profile, or delete your account entirely. To keep your Personal Data accurate, current, and complete, please update your profile or contact us as specified below. We will take reasonable steps to update or correct Personal Data in our possession that you have previously submitted via this Site.

Please also feel free to contact us if you have any questions about The Infatuation’s Privacy Policy or the information practices of this Site.

You may contact us as follows:

The Infatuation Inc.  
425 E. 13th St.  
#6J  
NY, NY 10009

info@theinfatuation.com
